[
  {
    "question_name":"1",
    "question": "HTML stands for?",
    "option1": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    "option2": "High Text Markup Language",
    "option3": "Hyper Tabuler Markup Language",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"2",
    "question": "Which of these tag is used to mark a begining of a paragraph?",
    "option1":"&lt td &gt",
    "option2":"&lt br &gt",
    "option3":"&lt p &gt",
    "option4":"&lt tr &gt",
    "answer":"&lt p &gt"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"3",
    "question": "From which tag descriptive list starts?",
    "option1":"&lt ll &gt",
    "option2":"&lt dd &gt",
    "option3":"&lt dl &gt",
    "option4":"&lt ds &gt",
    "answer":"&lt dl &gt"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"4",
    "question": "Correct HTML tag for largest heading is-",
    "option2":"&lt head &gt",
    "option1":"&lt h6 &gt",
    "option3":"&lt heading &gt",
    "option4":"&lt h1 &gt",
    "answer":"&lt h1 &gt"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"5",
    "question":"The attribute of <form> tag is-",
    "option1":"Method",
    "option2":"Action",
    "option3":"Both (a) & (b)",
    "option4":"None of these",
    "answer":"Both (a) & (b)"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"6",
    "question":"Markup tags tell the web browser-",
    "option1":"How to organise the page",
    "option2":"How to display the page",
    "option3":"How to display message box on page",
    "option4":"None of these",
    "answer":"How to display the page"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"7",
    "question": "www is based on which model?",
    "option1":"Local-server",
    "option2":"client-server",
    "option3":"3-tire",
    "option4":"None of these",
    "answer":"client-server"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"8",
    "question":"What are empty elements and is it valid?",
    "option1":"No, there is no such term",
    "option2":"Empty element is element with no data",
    "option3":"No, it is not valid to use empty element",
    "option4":"None of these",
    "answer":"Empty element is element with no data"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"9",
    "question":"Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum charecter?",
    "option1":"Size",
    "option2":"Len",
    "option3":"Maxlength",
    "option4":"All of these",
    "answer":"Maxlength"
  },
  {
    "question_name":"10",
    "question":"HTML is subset of-",
    "option1":"SGMT",
    "option2":"SGML",
    "option3":"SGMD",
    "option4":"None of these",
    "answer":"SGML"
  }
]
